pussy-dreams.com 2017-05-16

# Privacy Policy Pussy Video | Pussy Dreams

You care about how your personal information is used and shared. Pussy Dreams takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about the privacy policies of Pussy Dreams.

News.me is the company that operates the various Pussy Dreams sites, apps, services, content, features, and related products, such as the Pussy Dreams homepage, Pussy Dreams Video, Pussy Dreams Reader, the Daily Pussy Dreams, Pussy Dreams Dialog, and Pussy Dreams’s mobile applications. Collectively, in this document, we’ll refer to the suite of Pussy Dreams products and services as “Pussy Dreams”.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of News.me Inc. on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on Pussy Dreams. In connection with your use of Pussy Dreams, we receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) through your Pussy Dreams user account (your “Account”); (ii) your use of Pussy Dreams generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use Pussy Dreams, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, transmission, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

##### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) we gather when you are using or accessing Pussy Dreams. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third-party websites, content sources, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you choose to access through Pussy Dreams, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. Basically, our Privacy Policy applies to the thing we control; others’ privacy policies apply to the things they control.

While we endeavor to facilitate access only to Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we can’t, and don’t, take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access via Pussy Dreams.

##### What Information Is Collected by Pussy Dreams?

The information we gather enables us to operate, personalize, and improve Pussy Dreams. When you access some components of Pussy Dreams, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

###### Sign-In Information:

When you create an Account or login using your Twitter, Facebook, and/or Google credentials, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username on that service and/or email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account with Pussy Dreams and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous.

We may use contact information you voluntarily provide to send you information about our Services, including without limitation, notifications regarding the Services and, upon your consent, email digests of content shared by those that you follow on Pussy Dreams, Twitter, and/or Facebook. You may subscribe and unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we regardless reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

###### User Content and URL Information:

Pussy Dreams allows you to provide content to Pussy Dreams, such as the ability to Pussy Dreams and Submit collections of content and uniform resource locators (“URLs”), written descriptions of content or URLs, comments, text, images and video, along with your Name, Username, avatar, and profile bio.

We may also collect and store information regarding the content dugg, submitted, or shared to your Pussy Dreams, Twitter, and/or Facebook, and the original URL, and associate that information with your Account. We also collect and store (i) the time and date on which the content was first dugg, submitted, or shared and (ii) information on the channels through which the content was shared, e.g., to other Pussy Dreams users, Twitter followers, and/or Facebook friends.

Your Pussy Dreams name, username, bio, and avatar and your comments on Pussy Dreams are always public. We share certain information about you when you choose to make other information public through the account settings page, such as your Twitter handle (which is displayed on the public page for your Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter content), your reading feeds through Pussy Dreams, your Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter stories, Twitter, your Saved items, and other information you elect to make public to your followers on Twitter, your friends on Facebook, and/or any other Third Party Services you use. This may include Personal Information, but only to the extent that you decide to share such information with others.

We may retain data submitted by you to Pussy Dreams indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account.

###### Pussy Dreams Reader Information:

If you are a Pussy Dreams Reader user, we will maintain information about the sources and subscriptions, including RSS and other content feeds, that you choose to follow. We will collect and store (i) all articles and posts that are part of your subscribed feeds, (ii) data associated with those items, such as the time and date they were published, (iii) whether and when you viewed, saved, or marked them as read, (iv) information related to your organizational choices, such as the folders or tags you assign to sources, and (v) information necessary to complete actions you may choose to take with particular items, such as Pussy Dreamsing, saving, liking, recommending, or sharing to Third Party Services.

###### Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter Information:

If you are a user of Pussy Dreams Deeper (a.k.a., Top Twitter Stories), we will maintain information about your Twitter social graph, as well as the Tweets that appear in your Twitter timeline. We will collect and store (i) all Tweets that are part of your Twitter timeline, (ii) data associated with those Tweets, such as the time and date they were published, (iii) whether and when you viewed, saved, or marked as read your Top Twitter stories, (iv) information necessary to complete actions you may choose to make with particular Top Twitter stories, such as Pussy Dreamsing, saving, liking, recommending, or sharing to Third Party Services.

###### Metrics and Analytics:

We collect information about accesses of content curated through Pussy Dreams, as well as interactions with Pussy Dreams Reader, Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter, and other Pussy Dreams features and services. This information includes, but is not limited to: (i) the IP address and physical location of the devices accessing the curated content or interacting with Pussy Dreams; (ii) the time and date of each access or interactions; and (iii) information about sharing of curated content or content appearing on or accessed through Pussy Dreams.

###### Information Collected From Third Party Services:

Some features of Pussy Dreams allow you to share content accessed through Pussy Dreams to Third Party Services, as well as your content through Third Party Services to Pussy Dreams. If you choose to connect Pussy Dreams to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of those Third Party Services, such as authentication tokens that allow us to connect to your Third Party Service accounts. We may otherwise collect information about how you are using Pussy Dreams to interact with those connected Third Party Services. Note that Third Party Services may have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us.

We use Google Analytics to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics provides us with information such as how often people visit, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. To accomplish this, Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, but not your name or other identifying information. Google Analytics also places a permanent cookie on your web browser to define user sessions and recognize you as a return user the next time you visit this site.

We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis, which means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that website. The data collected cannot be retrieved by services from other domains.

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits by disabling cookies in your browser or deleting the Google Analytics cookies. You can also manage your settings for Google Analytics and opt-out of this feature by visiting Google.com Ad Settings or Google Analytics’ opt-out tools.

Pussy Dreams mobile applications (iOs and Android) use Localytics for demographic and interest-based information. You may wish to read Localytics’ privacy policy and/or use their opt-out service.

Pussy Dreams uses Chartbeat in order to measure engagement and help us make decisions about features or products we offer. If you would like to opt-out, you can delete some cookies from your browser as described in the Charbeat Privacy Policy.

Pussy Dreams uses Quantcast for information on Internet traffic statistics and demographic data. If you do not wish to participate, you may adjust your setting in Quantcast’s opt-out tool.

###### IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:

We automatically receive and record information from the Pussy Dreams application or your web browser when you interact with Pussy Dreams, including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with Pussy Dreams (e.g., what content you have clicked on).

Generally, Pussy Dreams automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of users accessing Pussy Dreams, Pussy Dreams features and applications, and its various streams of content. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of Pussy Dreams so that we can analyze and improve them.

###### Information Collected Using Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser or application when you access a website or service. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website or service you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser or Pussy Dreams application and tell us how and when you visit and use Pussy Dreams through the web or through an application.

Pussy Dreams cookies also allow us to track when you have accessed content through Pussy Dreams. Each access is tracked using a unique identifier assigned to you in one or more cookies stored by your web browser or application and associated with Pussy Dreams.

Pussy Dreams cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser or application has accessed content through Pussy Dreams and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer or device. For example, third party websites may set their own cookies.

###### Aggregate Information:

We collect statistical information about how people use Pussy Dreams (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information, such as your location (which, in turn, can be derived from your IP address or through location based services used by your device). This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account, your web browser or your Pussy Dreams application.

##### How and To Whom Is My Information Shared?

Pussy Dreams is designed to help you share information that you or people you choose to follow locate on the web. As a result, much of the information generated through Pussy Dreams is shared publicly or with third parties. All Pussy Dreams content is public. We may also distribute content and feeds through an email digest to users who have elected to receive such email digests.

###### Public Pussy Dreams Activity Information:

Your activity on the Pussy Dreams network is public by default and can be located by or distributed to anyone, although certain activity and information can be made private through your Account settings page (such as your Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter stories, Pussy Dreams Reader feed, items that you Pussy Dreams, and your Saved items). Individuals reading the aforementioned information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. Therefore, we urge you to think carefully about how you configure your Pussy Dreams settings, and what actions you take on Pussy Dreams.

###### Information You Elect to Share:

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, you should also review the terms of service and privacy policies of any Third Party Services that you access through Pussy Dreams. Pussy Dreams respects the privacy settings/policies that you have selected with Third Party Services, and only shares information consistent with those privacy settings and policies.

You may otherwise access Third Party Services through Pussy Dreams, for example by accessing curated content. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on or through Pussy Dreams.

###### User Profile Information:

User profile information, including the display Name you select, the username you choose to use on Pussy Dreams, avatars or images you elect to upload and other information you enter on your profile (such as your bio), may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within Pussy Dreams. Email addresses, Twitter, Facebook, and/or Google account name will not appear on your public profile unless you enter it in the bio area yourself.

###### Aggregate Information:

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use Pussy Dreams and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how we interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

###### Information Shared with Our Agents:

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

###### Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets associated with Pussy Dreams, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

###### Information Disclosed for the Protection of Us and Others:

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam prevention.

###### Information We Share With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

###### Email Communications:

If you sign up for The Daily Pussy Dreams email via the Pussy Dreams website or in any other Pussy Dreams application, you will receive an email once daily highlighting some curated or other content on Pussy Dreams. If you sign up for Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter email alerts or a daily summary email of your Pussy Dreams Deeper/Top Twitter stories, you may select frequency and/or timing of such emails through your settings page.

Regardless of whether you decide to receive the above mentioned email alerts, you may occasionally receive from us email and other communication relating to your Account. These emails will only be sent for important purposes, such as password recovery or important communications regarding Pussy Dreams services and/or features.

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve email deliverability and/or our customer service. You may wish to read the policy for use of cookies and other technologies used by Sailthru, our email provider. If you do not wish to receive emails from Pussy Dreams, you may unsubscribe from individual email communications through your settings page, or click the unsubscribe link in any email to cease all further email correspondence from Pussy Dreams.

##### Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information (including your Twitter, Facebook, Google or other third-party logins) is protected for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your passwords appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard security techniques. Although we undertake regular security review and use industry Best Practices to keep your information safe, we do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

##### What Information of Mine Can I Access?

You can access information associated with your Account by logging into the web version of Pussy Dreams, or through the Pussy Dreams application. You can adjust settings and privacy preferences through your Account settings.

##### How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by visiting your Account settings page. If you terminate and delete your Account, any association between your Account and information stored by, or in connection with, Pussy Dreams will no longer be accessible. However, given the nature of sharing using Pussy Dreams, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public. If you would like us to remove such stored information, please send us an email at [support@Pussy Dreams.com](mailto:support@digg.com).

##### What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

As stated previously, you can opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some Pussy Dreams features.

You can delete your Account or adjust your Account’s privacy settings. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible.

##### What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on or within Pussy Dreams or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses Pussy Dreams after such changes have been first posted.

##### What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using Pussy Dreams, please send us a detailed message to: [support@Pussy Dreams.com](mailto:support@digg.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

**Effective Date:** October 4, 2016.
